So, if you said exponential, you are correct.
指数と答えた人は正解です
Because this is a function that returns a positive number for every input.
これはすべての入力に対して正数を返す関数だからです
E to the X is always a positive number.
EのX乗は常に正数です
So, what we're going to do is exactly what we did before,
これから行うことは以前にしたこととまったく同じですが
except, applying it to the X to the scores.
点数にXを適用します
So, instead of 2,1, 0,
2 1 0の代わりに
we have E to the 2,
Eの2乗
E to the 1 and E to the 0.
Eの1乗 Eの0乗を使用します
So, that 2 becomes E to the 2 divided by E to the two plus E to the 1 plus E to the 0.
2はEの2乗÷Eの2乗＋Eの1乗＋Eの0乗になります
And, similarly for 1 and 0.
1と0についても同様です
So, the probabilities we obtain now are as 0.67, 0.24 and 0.09.
得られる確率は0.67 0.24 0.09になります
This clearly add to 1.
これは明らかに1に加えられます
And, also notice that since the exponential function is increasing,
また 指数関数は増加しているので
then the duck has a higher probability than the beaver.
アヒルはビーバーより高い確率を持ちます
And this one has a higher probability than the walrus.
ビーバーはセイウチより高い確率を持ちます
This function is called the Softmax function and it's defined formally like this.
この関数はsoftmax関数と呼ばれ 正式には次のように定義されます
Let's say we have N classes and a linear model that gives us the following scores.
Nクラスがあり次のような点数を与える線形モデルがあるとします
Z1, Z2, up to ZN.
Z1 Z2 ZNまで
Each score for each of the classes.
それぞれ各クラスの点数です
What we do to turn them into probabilities is to say
これを確率に変えます つまり
the probability that the object is in class I is going to be
オブジェクトがクラスiにある確率は
E to the power of the ZI divided by
EのZi乗を
the sum of E to the power of Z1 plus all the way to E to the power ZN.
EのZ1乗からEZn乗までの和で割ったものになります
That's how we turn scores into probabilities.
このようにして点数を確率に変換します
So, here's a question for you.
ここで問題です
When we had two classes,
2クラスがあり
we applied the sigmoid function to the scores.
点数にシグモイド関数を適用しました
Now, that we have more classes we apply the softmax function to the scores.
今度は さらに多くのクラスがあり 点数にsoftmax関数を適用します
The question is, is the softmax function
問題は nに対するsoftmax関数は
for N equals to the same as the sigmoid function?
シグモイド関数と同じになるかということです
I'll let you think about it. The answer is actually,
考えてみてください答えは実際には
yes, but it's not super trivial why.
「はい」ですが 理由は単純ではありません
And, it's a nice thing to remember.
覚えておくのは良いことです